（莫斯科）
（现今）
喂
Yes?
马上过去 别走
I'll be right there. Don't move.
想象一个资讯无法让人信任的世界
Imagine a world where information can't be trusted.
不难想象吧
Not very hard, is it?
新闻媒体说的是一回事
News service says one thing,
网站说的是另一回事
website says another.
社会开始起冲突
Society starts to fray.
我们只能向自己关心的人求助
All we can turn to are the people we care about.
但如果那些人跟我们想的不一样呢
But what if those people weren't who we thought they were?
如果我们最亲近的人
What if the ones closest to us,
我们将性命托付给他们的人
the ones we've trusted our whole lives...
根本是另一个人呢
...were someone else entirely?
（UKN24新闻）
如果他们根本不是人类呢
What if they weren't even human?
（波哥大恐攻 与抢案有关 ）
（慕尼黑恐攻 大规模枪击 动机 26死）
普瑞斯考探员 不好意思
Agent Prescod, respectfully...
你到底在说什么
uh, what exactly are you talking about?
混乱
Chaos.
这只是开始
And that's only the beginning.
去年发生了五起全球恐怖攻击
Five global terrorist strikes within the past year.
分别有不同团体声称犯案
Each one claimed by a different group.
通常都是如此
It's business as usual.
他们就是要你这么想
That's precisely what they want you to think.
阿根廷攻击哥伦比亚 哥伦比亚攻击菲律宾
Argentina attacks Colombia, Colombia attacks the Philippines.
暴力连锁效应扩及全球
A violent chain reaction consuming the globe.
你明白全世界陷入交战状态吗
Do you realize that the entire world is at war?
气氛确实很紧张
Well, the atmosphere has been tense.
有人在制造这种紧张气氛 罗斯探员
There is an architect to that tension, Agent Ross.
这些攻击逐步升高
These attacks are escalating.
如果他们攻击主要国家…
If they hit the soil of the major power...
你认为幕后主谋是同一批人
So you... You think the same people are behind all of this?
不是人
Not people...
是史克鲁尔人
Skrulls.
拜托 罗斯 你知道怎么回事
Come on, Ross, you know the stories.
这不是昨天才开始的
This didn't start yesterday.
在30年前史克鲁尔人 发现地球就开始了
It started 30 years ago when the Skrulls found Earth.
卡萝丹佛斯和尼克福瑞 答应为他们找到一个新的星球
Carol Danvers and Nick Fury promised to find them a new planet.
可是现在…
But now...
他们不要别的星球 要我们的
now they don't want just any planet, they want ours.
你还不懂吗
Look, can't you see it?
这些团体都一样
All these groups, they're the same.
史克鲁尔人能随时随地变成任何人
Skrulls could be anybody, anywhere, at any time.
目前只有一小群住在地球
And there is only a tiny handful known to live on Earth.
- 那根本不足以… - 怎样
- That's barely enough to... - To what?
你不知道自己在说什么 罗斯
You have no goddamn idea what you're talking about, Ross!
他们可能有几千 几万个
There could be thousands of them, tens of thousands!
你根本不会知道
And you would never know.
普瑞斯考 我们从大局着眼
Okay, Prescod, let's play a little game of forest for the trees, shall we?
对 史克鲁尔人能易形 对 他们在找新家
Yes, Skrulls can shapeshift. Yes, they're looking for a new home.
但就像你说的
But, as you say,
目前只能透过尼克福瑞联系史克鲁尔人
the only Skrull contact has been through Nick Fury.
这表示他们是我们的盟友
That means they're our allies.
那福瑞在哪里
Then where is Fury?
他在神刃太空站
He's on S.A.B.E.R.!
如果要为这种事叫他下来
God... And if I'm gonna bring him down for whatever the hell this is,
我不能只有推论 还需要证据
I need to give him something more than just theories, I need evidence.
其他这些攻击
All these other attacks,
跟这个比起来都是小儿科
they would be nothing compared to this.
这会让世界陷入无情战火
This is the one that sets the world on fire.
我不再向局里提出报告了 不晓得还能相信谁
I stopped filing reports at the office. Don't know who I can trust anymore.
除了你
Other than you...
普瑞斯考 我是来帮忙的
Hey, Prescod, look, I'm here to help. Okay?
我把这个带走 把情报交给福瑞
So... So let me take this and I'll give the information to Fury.
好吗
Okay?
好
Yeah.
我需要撤离 快
I need an extract. Fast.
我需要撤离
I need an extract.
（罗斯探员）
（学院站）
学院地铁站 西北方六个街区
Academica Metro Station, six blocks northeast.
罗斯
Ross.
手举高
Show me your hands.
- 塔洛斯 - 是我
- Talos. - It's me.
你怎么在这里
What the hell are you doing here?
我在追他
I'm chasing him.
他是你们的人
He was one of you.
不 他是…
No, he's...
他是他们那边的
He... He's one of them.
（根据漫威漫画改编）
《秘密入侵》
第一季第一集
本WEB版外挂字幕由  风吹来的那片云  双语合并
欢迎回地球
Welcome back to Earth.
他在楼上
He's upstairs.
家乡带来的吗
Is that from home?
山多米利卡
Santo Millika.
史克鲁尔的空气凤梨
That's a Skrull sky plant.
索伦到哪里都带着种子
Soren. She brought the seed with her wherever she went.
种了之后就变了 它适应了地球
And it's changed since she planted it. It's adapted to the planet.
嗯 你一向认为有可能
Yeah, well, you always believed that was possible.
我还是这么想
I still do.
我好遗憾
I am so sorry.
我也是
Me, too.
索伦很爱你
Soren loved you.
但她担心
But she worried, mate,
出这种事才能让你回地球
that it would take something like this to bring you back to Earth.
我想她说对了
And I guess she was right.
聊聊格拉威
Tell me about Gravik.
先聊你吧
Let's... Let's just talk about you first, yeah?
这些年来我们一直在帮你 确保你信守承诺
We've been helping you for all these years to ensure that you kept your promise.
但弹指事件后 你变了
But after The Blip, you were different.
然后消失无踪
And then you disappeared.
卡萝丹佛斯失踪了
Carol Danvers disappeared.
嘉雅也一样
And so did G'iah.
等等 你女儿 在哪失踪
Hold it. Your daughter? Disappeared too... Where?
她年纪轻
She was young.
气我们还没有家
Angry that our people still don't have a home.
许多人都很难过
Many of them are upset.
我被逐出议会 流落在外
I got kicked off the Council, pushed into exile.
可是 格拉威…
But, Gravik...
格拉威对你抛弃我们特别不满
Gravik, mate, he took your abandonment that much harder.
走吧
Come on.
格拉威是史克鲁尔议会的最新成员
Gravik is now the newest member of the Skrull Council.
善于利用年轻史克鲁尔难民的愤怒
He preys on the collective rage of young, displaced Skrulls.
他在哪
Where is his ass?
这里 他在俄罗斯
He's here. He's in Russia.
史克鲁尔人不怕辐射
Skrulls are immune to radioactivity
俄国有地球上最多的废弃核电厂
and Russia has the most abandoned nuclear plants on Earth.
问题是 这些电厂没有纪录
But here's the thing. These plants, they're not on the books.
我们不知道他在哪
And we don't know where he is.
他的计画我们还知道什么
Well, what else do we know about his plans?
他都规划好了
Well, he's already made them.
这是冒牌罗斯探员想掩盖的
This is what Agent Ross's imposter was trying to cover up.
普瑞斯考拦截到的脏弹示意图
Schematics for a dirty bomb intercepted by Prescod.
普瑞斯考在监视新的激进团体AAR
Prescod had been monitoring a new radical group called the AAR,
「抗俄美国人」
Americans Against Russia,
他认为是史克鲁尔人的 下一个恐怖攻击掩护者
which he believed to be the next Skrull front for a terrorist attack.
格拉威打算引发美俄大战吗
Gravik's trying to start a war between Russia and the United States?
那是普瑞斯考的论点
That was Prescod's theory.
他要用这枚炸弹来做
And he's gonna use this bomb to do it?
他有材料吗
Does he have the materials for that?
哈萨克的一个武器藏匿点
A weapons cache in Kazakhstan,
在普瑞斯考死亡当天遭突袭
raided the same day that Prescod was killed.
我们带你来是有原因的
We brought you here for a reason.
如果他成功了
If he succeeds, um,
你们人类就会灭绝
your species will cease to exist.
可恶
Shit.
我去散个步
I'm going for a walk.
晚上在莫斯科散步
You're going for a walk in Moscow at night?
你会引人注意
Well, you're gonna stand out.
总统先生 我们有状况
We have a situation, Mr. President.
- 什么事  - 福瑞探员
- Concerning? - Agent Fury.
刚收到他离开神刃太空站的消息
We've just received word that he's left S.A.B.E.R.
什么叫他离开神刃太空站
What do you mean, "He left S.A.B.E.R.?"
我能用别的说法 放弃 弃置…
Well, I can try to think of a different word. Abandoned, departed...
福瑞探员正在建立人类史上最复杂的
Agent Fury is building up the most complex aerospace defense system
航太防御系统
in the history of mankind.
- 他不能一走了之 - 我同意
- He can't just leave. - No, I agree, sir.
不幸的是
And unfortunately,
我们也拦截到希尔探员 传给福瑞探员的加密讯息
we also intercepted an encrypted message from Agent Hill to Agent Fury.
我们尚未解密 只知道他们是老朋友
We haven't been able to decode it yet, but we know they're old friends.
由于联系不上希尔或福瑞
Given the fact that I could reach neither Agent Hill nor Agent Fury,
他们等于擅离职守
they're effectively AWOL.
快去处理
Deal with it.
是
Yes, sir.
真刺激
This is so exciting.
我想想 莫斯科的高大黑人
Let's see, large Black man, Moscow.
不是尼克福瑞 就是保罗罗布森的幽灵
Well, it could either be Nick Fury, or the ghost of Paul Robeson.
好 头套拿掉
Okay, go ahead, take the hood off.
讨厌 我以为能欣赏 《老人河》的现场演唱
Oh! Damn, and I was hoping for a command performance of Ol' Man River.
我也很高兴见到你 桑雅
Good to see you too, Sonya.
怎么 你叫你的喽啰 用高明的手段把我引渡过来吗
So, did you just have me extraordinarily renditioned by a group of your thugs?
你们高明吗
Were you lot extraordinary?
你们的表现通常乏善可陈
You usually only scratch the surface of mediocrity.
看来终于开窍了 干得好
You must be finally putting it all together. Well done.
好 下去吧 没事了
Okay. You can go. That's... That'll do.
「高明」 好欣慰
"Extraordinary," well, that's wonderful.
真高兴见到你
It is so good to see you.
你容光焕发
You look amazing.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 喝酒吗  - 来一杯
- Drink? - Love one.
你有收集时钟的癖好
Do you have some sort of clock fetish that you've been
这些年都没让我知道
keeping from me all these years?
一个英国老特务头子开启这项传统
It was an old English spymaster that started the tradition.
退休时就挂一个钟
A clock goes up when your time in circus is done.
我觉得自己还有一些任务未完成
And I like to think I still have a few juggling acts left in me.
当自己家 福瑞
Oh. Make yourself at home, Fury.
相信你记得我爱喝波本酒
I'm pretty sure you recollect my drink of choice as bourbon.
我本来想欢迎你回家
I might have welcomed you home,
但我还没忘掉你摧毁我的高级公寓
but I still haven't forgiven you for destroying my expensive flat.
你是指城市
You mean city.
只能请你喝便宜的酒
It's bottom shelf piss for you or nothing.
你在莫斯科做什么
So, what are you doing in Moscow?
跟你一样 趁早弭平史克鲁尔人叛乱
Same as you, trying to kill the Skrull rebellion in its crib.
你认识叛军领袖吧
You know the rebel leader personally, don't you?
以前认识
I knew him.
所以你才从太空站下来吗
Is that why you came down from your space station?
你觉得你要负责吗
You feel responsible?
对于发生在哈萨克
What do you know about a heist
一处黑市仓库的抢案 你知道多少
at a black market storage facility in Kazakhstan?
几天前的事
It happened couple days ago.
没印象
Doesn't ring a bell.
我也许看不出史克鲁尔人假装成人类
You know, I may not know when a Skrull is pretending to be a human,
但绝对能分辨人类在说谎
but I sure as hell know when a human is lying.
你很清楚那个仓库里有什么
You know damn well what was in that storage vault.
既然你不知道
The fact that you don't know
就表示新的尼克福瑞大不如前
tells me all I need to know about this new, rather old Nick Fury.
萨诺斯手指一弹 改变了你
I think that Thanos's snap changed you.
让你知道不论多努力为正义而战
Taught you that no matter how hard you fight for what's right,
总是有更强的人能击败你
there's always someone stronger to undermine you.
你似乎忘了旧的尼克福瑞
You seem to forget this "old Nick Fury"
有30年跟史克鲁尔人交手的经验
has 30 years of hands-on experience with the Skrulls.
我对这项威胁的了解远远超过你
I know the nature of this threat way better than you ever will.
你是在提议我们应该合作吗
Is that your idea of an offer of some sort of collaboration between us?
我们以前合作无间啊
We used to work pretty well together back in the day.
当年你大老远就会发现
Back then, you would've seen my rather mediocre bag men
我那些平庸的喽啰
coming a mile away.
你没事先发现
The fact that you didn't see them
可见你无法预料到 格拉威和他的叛军造反
means you haven't a hope in hell of seeing Gravik and his rebels coming.
所以跟你合作毫无意义
Which makes you as a partner rather pointless.
我让你的手下抓我是为了见你
I let your men take me so I could get to you.
我以朋友身分劝你 回你的太空站
I mean this as a friend, Fury, but go back to your space station.
你不适合参与眼前的战争
You're in no shape for this fight that lies before us.
我请我的喽啰送你回藏匿点
I'll have one of my thugs drop you back at the safe house.
不用了 我用走的
That's all right, I'll walk.
如果你想起哈萨克的事
If your memory jogs about that Kazakhstan thing,
打给我
call a brother.
（莫斯科西南方312公里）
你想干嘛
What do you want?
以真面目回家
Home in my own skin.
恢复你原本的模样
Take your natural form.
欢迎来到新史克鲁尔星
Welcome to New Skrullos.
叫什么名字
What's your name?
比托
Beto.
多久没吃东西了 比托
When's the last time you ate, Beto?
不知道
I don't know.
不会吧
This can't be.
这里只种史克鲁尔作物
We grow only Skrull produce here.
喝史克鲁尔酒 展现真实的面貌
Drink Skrull wine, wear Skrull skins.
不管你冒了什么险才来 都值得
Whatever dangers you risked getting here, know, they're worth it.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're very welcome.
现在超过500人了
We're over 500 strong now.
每个人都参加…
So, is everyone a part of...
反抗军 没有 格拉威提供庇护
The resistance? No. Gravik provides refuge.
但如果选择当战士 有一个好处
But if you do choose to be a warrior, there is one advantage.
是什么
Oh, yeah? What's that?
你可以离开
You get to leave.
其他人只能待在园区里
Everyone else stays in the compound.
战士能保留人形 外貌维持越久
The warriors keep our human form, the longer we're attached to our shells,
就越不可能被人类 和史克鲁尔同胞认出来
the less likely we can be identified by humans and Skrulls alike.
在这里等 有人会带你去房间
Wait here and someone will get you a proper room.
证明你的忠诚 格拉威会奖励你
Prove your loyalty and Gravik will reward you.
那后面是什么
What's behind there?
胜利
Victory.
叫什么名字
What is your name?
战士
Warrior.
为什么而战
What is your fight?
史克鲁尔星
Skrullos.
你有什么梦想
What is your dream?
以真面目回家
Home in my own skin.
把他的人形带来
Bring him his shell.
不要
No. No!
抗俄美国人 你的美梦快成真了
Americans Against Russia, your dreams are about to come true.
用他的脸
Take his face.
不
No!
接收他的心智
Now take his mind.
史克鲁尔人已渗透到主要强权的高层
Skrulls have infiltrated the ranks of major world powers.
证据在哪
Where is the proof?
福瑞探员回地球算吧
How about the arrival of Agent Fury?
他发誓远离地球 回来一定有原因
For a man who sworn off Earth, he would not have returned without cause.
说得没错
You got that right.
格拉威应该有杀手锏
Gravik has something very big up his sleeve.
但眼前的威胁依然是炸弹
But the immediate threat remains the bombs.
莫斯科有五名专家能制造这种炸弹
Five specialists in Moscow are capable of building such an explosive.
我敢说这个人就是
My money's on this one.
瓦西利帕希金 前车臣叛军
Vasily Poprishchin. Former Chechnyan rebel,
在市中心拥有一家高档艺廊
owns a high-end gallery in the city center,
储藏粉彩画和辐射炸弹
restores pigmented paintings and radioactivated bombs.
立刻展开突袭
Send in a raid now.
如果你说的立刻是指
If by "now" you mean,
等史克鲁尔叛军带着追踪装置
"Wait until a Skrull rebel picks up a device
带领我们回到他们的藏匿处 那我完全认同
in order to follow them to their hideout," then, yes, I totally agree.
她真不要脸
She's cheeky.
对 等她见到你这种丑史克鲁尔人
Yeah, 'till she sees an ugly-ass Skrull like you.
就会展开猎杀
Then she goes into hunting mode.
我在我们同类里算好看的
I'm considered good-looking amongst my kind.
我认识不少好看的史克鲁尔人 你不算
I know a bunch of good-looking Skrull. And you ain't one of them.
好啦 有什么计画
All right, guys, what is the play here?
我们去找那个俄国炸弹专家
I say we visit this Rusky bomb builder.
桑雅会安排探员过去
Sonya will already have agents there.
我们会阻止他们
Who we will incapacitate.
等一下
Hold on, stop.
你是说攻击军情六处情报员
You're talking about attacking MI6 operatives?
塔洛斯 我解释给你听
Talos, let me explain something to you.
我们不再只是对抗格拉威
We're no longer in "just a war" with Gravik.
而是与桑雅法斯沃竞争 她打算采取焦土政策
We are in a race with Sonya Falsworth, who celebrates a scorched-Earth policy,
只要是听过格拉威这名字的人
meaning, she will annihilate any and everyone
她会格杀勿论
who's ever even heard the name "Gravik."
想救无辜的史克鲁尔人 难免有人遭殃
You wanna save innocent Skrulls, you'll have to hurt some people.
好吧
All right...
格拉威知道
Look, Gravik knows that...
仁慈是你的弱点
mercy's your weakness.
你该证明他看走眼了
Time for you to prove him wrong.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
福瑞来了
Fury's in town, G.
（了解人类）
是吗
Is he?
我们的人说不必担心
Our man says it's nothing to worry about.
他身手大不如前 跛脚 视力不好
He's washed up, walks with a limp, can barely see with the good eye.
原来这件事你只让自己人知道
I see you've kept the circle tight on this one.
我们就是自己人 没别人
We're the circle. No one else.
是为了保护我还是目标
Is that to protect me, or the cause?
你就等于目标
You are the cause.
我不是
I'm not the cause.
目标是家
Cause is home.
是
Yes, sir.
明天出发 不夺下地球绝不罢休
We go tomorrow and we don't stop until Earth is ours.
- 怎样  - 这里好大
- What about it? - This place is massive.
你
You.
跟我来
Come with me.
泽克苏载你
Zirksu will drive you.
把现金送去这个地址
You take the cash to this address.
只能找帕希金
You deal with Poprishchin and no one else.
他会给你两个背包
He'll give you two bags.
原封不动送去莫斯科藏匿点
You get 'em to the Moscow safe house undisturbed and intact.
咖啡呢
Where's the bloody coffee?
军情六处状况如何
What's our MI6 status?
搞定
All set.
你是帕希金
You Poprishchin?
- 靠 - 让我来
- Oh, shit. - I got it, mate.
136岁还是一尾活龙
Not bad for a 136-year-old.
换成人类我不到40岁
Well, you know, I'm not even 40 in human years.
还没展开中年危机疯狂大采购
I haven't even gone on my midlife crisis shopping spree yet.
喂
Hey.
你当时买了什么
What'd you get for yours?
复仇者联盟
The Avengers.
你们一定迷路了
入口在马路上
不是 我们不要你的鬼画
No, mate, we don't want any of your shitty paintings.
那你们要什么
Then exactly what do you want?
诚实的答案
Some damn good answers.
我看到可疑分子
I've got eyes on a possible person of interest.
我跟过去 再向你报告
Initiating foot pursuit. I'll keep you posted.
随时回报
Yeah, just keep me informed.
抱歉 麻烦改天再来
I'm sorry, but you gentlemen will have to call at another time.
- 我快迟到了 - 你要去见谁
- I'm late for an appointment. - Oh! Oh, who you meetin' with?
我老婆 你是…
My wife, Mister...
真舒服
Ooh! Damn, this is nice.
那是路易十五的椅子 无价之宝
That chair belonged to Louis XV. It's priceless.
被子弹打烂前 什么都是无价之宝
Everything is priceless till it gets blown to bits in a hail of bullets.
凯勒探员 档案里有说这家伙有老婆吗
Agent Keller, anything in our file about this one having a wife?
有一个前妻
Yeah, has an ex-wife,
跟一个足球员住在迈阿密
lives in Miami with a soccer player.
所以他在撒谎啰
Oh, so we gonna go ahead and call that a lie.
人人都有一次机会
Everybody gets one.
没人有两次机会
Nobody gets two.
最后一次机会
So, last chance.
你要去见谁
Who are you going to meet?
到展示间会舒服一点
Perhaps we'd all be more comfortable in the gallery space
采光比较好
where there is more natural light.
那里有更多舒服的路易十四椅吗
You got any more of these comfortable-ass Louis XIV chairs in there?
脏弹呢
How about a dirty bomb?
还是你藏在这里的箱子里
Or you keep that in a crate in here somewhere?
抱歉 我没听过那种东西 脏弹
I'm sorry, I do not know this term. Dirty bomb?
砰 又爆炸了 第二个谎言
Boom, goes the dynamite! Lie number two.
我刚说了 人人有一次机会 没有两次
I just told you. Everybody gets one, nobody gets two.
你要开枪射我吗
You going to shoot me?
也许喔 应该会
Maybe. Well, probably.
但不是现在
But not right now.
炸弹在哪里
Where are the bombs?
你不叫凯勒
Your name's not Keller.
史克鲁尔人
Skrull.
你叫塔洛斯
Your name is Talos.
塔洛斯
Talos?
我没问题
I got this.
你确定
You sure?
这是我的局
This is my fight!
叫你别插手
I said no!
告诉我炸弹在哪里
Tell me where the bombs are!
你背叛自己的同胞
You betray your own people.
起来
Come on.
我叫你别管
I said no.
他去哪
Where'd he go?
她
She.
站住 站住 站住
Stop! Stop! Stop!
最后警告
Last warning!
你都这么说 但总有下一个警告
It's what you always say but there's always another.
嘉雅
G'iah.
- 炸弹给我 - 不要
- Give me the bombs. - No.
我知道你很生气 你不是这种人
I know you're angry. This isn't you.
这不是你母亲要的
This is not what your mother would've wanted.
我妈不知道她要什么
Mum doesn't know what she wants.
她的遗言是：「找到嘉雅」
Her last words, "Find G'iah."
什么
What?
她死了
She's dead.
怎么死的
How?
不如去问你的老大
Why don't you ask the people that you work for?
不如…拜托把炸弹交给我
Why don't you just give me the bomb, please?
嘉雅 炸弹给我
G'iah, give me the bomb.
- 不行 - 交出来
- I can't. - Just hand it over.
你就能走掉
And you'll walk away.
你知道我会保护你
'Cause you know that I'll protect you.
- 你谁都保护不了 - 嘉雅 我知道…
- You can't protect anyone. - G'iah, I know...
晚安 女士
等一下
尽量看
但你永远不会变成以前的你
你说什么 同志
给我波本和啤酒
另外看我朋友想喝什么
伏特加
跟在地乡亲交朋友
Making friends with the locals?
你想怎样能让冷战不变热战
How do you think we kept the Cold War from going hot?
我黑鬼请喝酒
Spooks like me buying shots.
你不能这么说
You can't say that.
不 是你不能这么说
No. You can't say that.
很高兴你回来 福瑞
It's good to have you back, Fury.
你是真心的 还是说场面话
Is that sincere or you just covering your bases?
要说说为何抛弃地球吗
You'll tell me why you abandoned Earth?
扩建神刃太空站
Well, building out S.A.B.E.R.
通常下棋时都要说实话
Traditionally, we tell the truth during our chess games.
也许那也变了 不晓得
Maybe that has changed too, though, I don't know.
应该说我有信心危机
Okay, let's just say I had a crisis of faith.
那干嘛回来
So why'd you come back?
它跟我跟到上头
It followed me up there,
而且我欠塔洛斯
and I owe it to Talos.
你确定不是在说别人吗
You sure you're not talking about someone else?
你会行动吗
You gonna move?
还没决定
I haven't decided.
我就担心这个
See, that's what I'm worried about.
我认识的福瑞总是未雨绸缪
The Fury I knew was always three steps ahead.
如果我记得没错 是你打给我
If I remember correctly, you called me.
应塔洛斯的要求
Upon Talos's request.
你过去几年不联络 意思很清楚
Your lack of contact over the past few years sent a pretty clear message.
什么意思
Meaning?
你还没准备好 福瑞
You're not ready for this, Fury.
威胁迫在眉睫
There's a very real threat out there.
弹指事件后 你完全变了
You were never the same after The Blip.
你总是告诉我 如果没把握
You always told me there is no shame
认输并不丢脸
in walking away when the steps are uncertain.
注意你的状况
So check your footing.
否则有人会受伤
Otherwise someone's gonna get hurt.
不
Oh, no.
妈的…
Mother...
干得好
Good work.
我差点逃不掉 有人在等我
I barely made it out. Someone was waiting for me.
是你认得的人吗
Someone you can identify?
不是
No.
也许该把攻击延后
Maybe we postpone the strike.
正好相反 多亏你 我们有了诱饵
To the contrary. Thanks to you, we have the bait.
谢谢你来见我
Thanks for coming to see me.
你没见到我 我没来
You don't see me because I'm not here.
我了解 你冒险前来
I understand. You're taking a risk.
冒险
A risk?
你这样跟我妈说吗 跟着你会害死她
Is that what you explained to Mum, that following you could get her killed?
你妈死的时候 你正在为凶手效命
Your mother died while you were working for her killer.
别扯到那边去 嘉雅
So do not take me down that road, G'iah.
你有一次机会救自己
You have one chance to save yourself.
我想你明白
And I think you know that.
所以你才会来
I think that's why you're here.
攻击预定在明天
The attack is planned for tomorrow.
团结日
Unity Day.
有三枚炸弹 格拉威知道你会到
There are three bombs. And Gravik knows you'll be there.
- 怎么会  - 我不知道
- How? - I don't know.
现场有好多特务 至少一百个
There are so many operatives in the field. A hundred, at least.
心智汲取站
Fracking pods?
他们身分大多保密 连我们也不知道
Most of their identities are kept secret, even from us.
你妈会很骄傲你来见我
Your mum would be very proud of you, you know, for coming to see me.
明天会有三个传递员 包括我
Tomorrow, there are three couriers, including me.
交付点都在统一广场附近
All the points near Vossoyedineniye Square.
我会用红外线喷雾在背包上做记号
I'll mark each bag with infrared spray.
嘉雅回来了
G'iah's come back.
我看到她了
I got eyes on her.
两个背包
Two backpacks.
让我来
I got her.
记住我们追的是背包 不是人
Remember we're tracking the bags, not the people.
莫斯科市中心好多背包
Lot of backpacks in Central Moscow.
嘉雅用红外线喷雾做记号
G'iah's painted ours with infrared spray.
红外线 了解
Infrared. Got it.
我们错过交接了
We missed the pass.
有个传递员往东北走
Got one carrier going northeast.
另一个往南 出动
The other one south. Let's move.
借过…
Excuse me. Excuse me!
空的 他们是诱饵
It's empty. They're decoys.
希尔
Hill!
- 玛丽亚 - 是你
- Maria! - It was you.
不是我
Not me.
字幕翻译：Aaron Wu